It's not easy having yourself a good time
这并不是一个休闲的游戏
Greasing up those bets and betters
射爆那些宝箱怪
Watching out they don't four-letter
注意自己死的时候别说脏话
F*ck and kiss you both at the same time
<del>就像抓钩</del>一样亲吻你的同时*你
Smells like something I've forgotten
闻起来像我已遗忘的<del>烤肉</del>
Curled up died and now it's rotten
<del>胡桃夹子</del>卷起的尸体现在已经腐烂
I'm not a gangster tonight
今晚我并不是<del>电鞭</del>流氓
Don't wanna be a bad guy
不想做<del>堕落的</del>坏人
I'm just a loner baby
我只是个<del>爱好触手的</del>孤独的孩子
And now you've gotten in my way
而挡着我的人只能选择死亡<del>之球</del>
I can't decide
我决定不了
Whether you should live or die
你该活着还是死去
Oh, you'll probably go to heaven
噢 也许你会升上天堂
Please don't hang your head and cry
请不要垂下头哭喊
No wonder why
怪不得
My heart feels dead inside
我的内心像死了一样
It's cold and hard and petrified
它寒冷 坚硬 石化了
Lock the doors and close the blinds
锁上门 拉上窗帘
We're going for a ride
我们出去兜风吧
It's a b*tch convincing people to like you
<del>大剑</del>你这家伙让人又爱又恨
If I stop now call me a quitter
如果现在我停下来<del>不踹你</del> 我会被叫做懦夫
If lies were cats you'd be a litter
如果谎言是猫 那么你就是垃圾
Pleasing everyone isn't like you
讨好所有人并不像<del>集束炸弹</del>你的风格
Dancing jigs until I'm crippled
我能<del>穿着Hayabusa之鞋</del>快步跳着 直到变成跛子
Slug ten drinks I won't get pickled
我能喝下十杯<del>血瓶</del>酒而丝毫不醉
I've got to hand it to you
我要把它交给你
You've played by all the same rules
你被全部相同的<del>血量</del>规则玩弄了
It takes the truth to fool me
用“<del>隐身</del>真相”来愚弄我
And now you've made me angry
现在你让我<del>暴击</del>愤怒了
I can't decide
我决定不了
Whether you should live or die
你该活着还是死去
Oh, you'll probably go to heaven
噢 也许你会升上天堂
Please don't hang your head and cry
请不要垂下头哭喊
No wonder why
怪不得
My heart feels dead inside
我的内心像死了一样
It's cold and hard and petrified
它寒冷 坚硬 石化了
Lock the doors and close the blinds
锁上门 关上窗帘
We're going for a ride
我们出去兜风吧
Oh, I could throw you in the lake
噢 我可以把你扔进<del>油腻的</del>湖里
Or feed you poisoned birthday cake
或者喂你吃有毒的生日蛋糕
I won't deny I'm gonna miss you when you're gone
我不否认 当你离开之后 我想念你<del>的金牙</del>
Oh, I could bury you alive
噢 我可以把你活埋<del>到刺里</del>
But you might crawl out with a knife
但你也许会拿着刀子爬出来
And kill me when I'm sleeping
在我<del>眩晕时</del>睡觉时杀我
That's why
这就是为什么
I can't decide
我不能决定
Whether you should live or die
你该活着还是死去
Oh, you'll probably go to heaven
噢 也许你会升上天堂
Please don't hang your head and cry
请不要垂下头哭喊
No wonder why
怪不得
My heart feels dead inside
我的内心像死了一样
It's cold and hard and petrified
它寒冷 坚硬 石化了
Lock the doors and close the blinds
锁上门 拉上窗帘
We're going for a ride
我们出去兜风吧
BGM: I can't decide by Scissor Sisters
由Bolshevik0制作